[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
[Ivy] It's true! I am
the traitor in your family!
I, Ivy Aguas, am the traitor
in the Ardiente family!
Ivy Aguas is on our side.
She is the heart, mind,
and soul of our cause.
[Julio] Miss Aguas!
You can't escape now.
We set the trap,
and you jumped right into it.
You really are a traitor.
And we were right all along.
Now, no snake will leave this place alive.
Don't celebrate just yet
because I'm not through with you!
If Lily really were fine,
she would've called ages ago.
[Anna] What's our next move against Julio?
-[gunshot]
-[Pandoy] He's pretty tough.
He's like a fearless action star.
Just like you.
He's the man we need
to take down the Ardientes.
[Jepoy] All that matters to me
is killing Julio Ardiente and Jaguar
so I can protect the ones I love.
If you want her, go ahead.
You can have her.
I want Arnaldo to see that woman die.
[Emilia] It's a done deal.
I shall see you, then. [laughing]
This is it.
[phone ringing]
[Raul] Diego.
Dad?
Why did you call, son?
Dad, I'm sorry, but there's
no one else I can turn to.
I need your help.
What is it?
Just say the word and I'll help you.
Dad, Ivy's missing.
Do you have any idea where she is?
The last thing we know
is that she was
on her way to the Ardientes'.
Dad, please, help us.
We can't find Ivy.
I'm here at the mansion,
but she isn't here.
Why? Is something wrong?
I have a feeling
they've done something to her.
Hold on. Why are you
so worried about Ivy Aguas?
Isn't she your enemy?
She's on Julio's side.
Dad, Ivy is important to me.
Okay, I'll help you.
I'll see if they have anything
to do with her disappearance.
Thank you.
Thank you, Dad.
[unsettling music playing]
Diego, why did you call your father?
Anna, I'm desperate.
We have to know where Ivy is.
Your father is connected
to Julio and Emilia.
What if he tells them
you're in touch with Lily?
You'll be putting her life in danger.
Wake up, Anna.
Ivy's life has always been in danger.
So, I don't care if they
discover her identity anymore.
We have to do something now
because if we don't,
we might never see her alive.
[unsettling music playing]
Thank you.
Oh, there they are. Hello, Papa.
[Julio] Hello, Emilia, my dear.
Oh, my son, Arnaldo.
-Welcome.
-Yes, I brought him along.
[Emilia chuckles] It's gonna be exciting.
Uh…
Interesting choice of location.
What do you have in store for us?
[laughs] Papa, you're gonna love this.
Today marks the death of Miss Ivy Aguas.
-[Emilia squeals]
-Is she really dying today?
-Yes, Papa.
-Oh, my. I don't believe this.
You monsters.
You're worse than the devil himself!
You're all monsters!
Shh! Quiet. Quiet. Quiet.
You witch!
I'm going to give you your last blessing,
so you should shut up.
Come on, let us all pray.
[grunts]
[Emilia] We are gathered here
for the soul of our friend, Ivy Aguas,
who's gonna be in a
better place than any of us.
In a place where she will stay
forever and ever in…
…hell! [laughs]
Oh. Finally.
[Emilia] There you go.
Put her in the coffin.
Colonel, would you like to help them?
You're finally going to die.
You bastards! What are you gonna do?
Let go of me!
Hey! You bastards! Let go of me!
-[Emilia laughs]
-What are you going to do?!
-Goodbye, Miss Aguas.
-Let me go!
What are you doing, huh?!
-Get off!
-[Emilia laughing]
-[Julio] She is feisty.
-[Emilia] Oh.
[Julio] Up to her last breath,
-she's feisty.
-I know, Papa.
You're monsters!
[Emilia] Papa, wait! Papa! Please!
Damn you, Emilia! You witch!
-Oh, please! No!
-You witch!
[Ivy screaming] You witch!
She's going to die now. Oh!
[Ivy] Damn you, Emilia!
[fake crying]
[hysterical laugh]
Monsters! Damn you, Ardientes!
-Oh, come, come, come.
-[Ivy] I hate you, Emilia!
[Ivy] Curse you! Go to hell!
-[Emilia fake crying]
-[Ivy] You'll pay for this!
You better get ready
because I'll have my revenge!
Please don't leave me, Ivy.
Please! [fake crying]
You think this is the last of me?!
It doesn't end here! You bastards!
-[Emilia laughs hysterically]
-Get this over with.
[fake crying] Ivy!
I'm gonna miss you, I swear.
[fake crying]
Don't! Don't! Don't! Don't!
Don't stop. Go on.
[laughs hysterically]
[grunts]
[Emilia laughs hysterically]
[grunting and panting heavily]
-[Ivy] No, please!
-[Julio] I see it.
But it's like I can't believe it.
She really is going to get buried.
[ominous music playing]
-[fire blazing]
-[people crying]
[grunts]
Adios, Ivy Aguas.
[whimpers]
[Emilia] Oh, Ivy.
May you rest in peace, and
bless your unfortunate soul.
-We will miss you.
-[lighter clicks]
[panting heavily]
[breathing raggedly] You damn Ardientes!
[tense music playing]
You bastards!
[sobbing]
You monsters! I hate you all!
Curse you, damn Ardientes!
Curse you!
[Ivy] You'll all to hell!
I hate you all!
[Ivy crying] You are monsters!
Go to hell, Ardientes!
Damn you!
[sobbing]
[tense music continues]
May you rest in peace, Ivy Aguas.
Can you please help me?
You're so slow.
My heels! Ouch!
[bangs on wood, grunting]
[tense music playing]
[clapping]
Emilia, you have
outdone yourself this time.
You have proven yourself
beyond all my imagination.
Truly, you have Ardiente blood
running in your veins.
And now, that this whole brouhaha is over,
we can focus our attention
on the centennial celebration
of the founding day of my…
I mean, of our province.
-[Emilia sighs]
-[Julio] Poblacion Ardiente.
Yes! [claps]
Papa, it's so exciting.
Quadruple celebration!
First, because you were elected governor.
Second, because I've been acquitted
of all my charges.
Third, because Ivy Aguas
is finally laid to rest.
And fourth, because we're celebrating
our province's 100th year, Papa!
-A quadruple celebration!
-Yes! [laughs]
-Viva Ardiente!
-Life is so good!
Papa, it's so good.
Hashtag, "blessed".
-Viva Ardiente!
[laughs]
Goodbye, Ivy Aguas!
[tense music playing]
[grunting]
[breathing raggedly]
[solemn music playing]
[bangs]
[breathing raggedly]
[banging and crying]
You monsters!
Damn you, Ardientes!
Curse you!
Damn you!
[solemn music continues]
[sniffles]
[bangs]
Ivy.
You have five hours.
That's the longest
you can survive in here.
Ivy, you can still get out.
If Emilia and the rest
of the Ardientes think
you can't get out of here,
Ivy, they're wrong.
They're dead wrong.
I will get out of here!
I know it. I will get out of here, Emilia.
You will get out of here, Ivy!
[thunder rumbling]
What the--
[solemn music playing]
[thunder rumbling]
-[Emilia squeals]
-[Julio] Let's go!
[Emilia] It's raining.
Damn it!
-[Emilia exclaims]
-Let's go!
[banging and crying]
-[Lily] Monsters!
-[banging continues]
[Ivy] You monsters!
I need the revised program
by noon tomorrow, Kelly.
[snickers]
Remember, this is an important day
for Poblacion Ardiente.
This is our centennial celebration.
And this is our opportunity
to show the Philippines
that this province still belongs to us.
-[chuckles]
-Clear?
[Emilia snickers]
Emilia, are you with us?
Yes, Papa, I am.
You seem to be in too much
of a good mood today.
I've noticed you were
just smiling the whole time.
That's not it, Papa.
I'm just thinking that
the centennial celebration
should be exciting and fun
with all the fireworks!
Why would you let the people endure
your long boring speeches, Papa?
Listen, Emilia,
if you have nothing good
to contribute to this program,
there's the door. Get out!
Get out! Get out!
Get out!
[Emilia] Wow, why is this
old man so irritable?
What did you say?
Huh?
Nothing.
[Emilia laughs] It's just boring speeches.
-[door closes]
-I have a nut for a daughter.
[tense music playing]
-[grunts]
-[soft thud]
[cloth rips]
[unsettling music playing]
[grunts]
[cloth ripping]
[tense music playing]
[man] One-two, three-four.
[bangs loudly]
Help! Help!
-Five, six, seven, eight!
-Help! Help!
Eight, seven, six, five,
four, three, two, and one.
One, two, three, four…
[bangs] Help me!
Help!
Hey! Did you guys hear that?
Help! I'm trapped here!
Somebody help me!
-I'm trapped here!
-There!
Help!
-Ghost!
-[screams]
[banging and sobbing]
Help! Please help me!
Help!
[cocks firearm]
Looks like somebody is
having fun with his new toys.
Don't worry, there's more
where that came from.
We're going to need more than guns and men
if we really want
to take down the Ardientes.
I know.
Don't worry, help will come soon.
[phone ringing]
Just a minute, ma'am.
-Hello?
-Jepoy, get over here now.
We need you.
Why, Anna? What's the problem?
Lily's still missing.
[tense music playing]
Ma'am, I have to go.
Where are you going?
I have to take care of something.
Lily Cruz…
and the gang?
The good guys? [scoffs]
I can't stand them.
They're so annoying.
Ma'am, I just have to handle this.
Madrigal.
I don't like sharing
my friends with others.
And I don't like sharing you.
The day will come
when you'll have to choose…
where your loyalties lie.
With your friends?
[tense music playing]
Or with me?
Them or me?
[tense music continues]
[door opens and closes]
Jaguar, my favorite cat, how are you?
You sound too happy, Emilia.
No. I just miss you, Jaguar.
-Hmm.
-[chuckles]
How are you? It's been a long time.
And you are right.
I'm actually savoring the moment.
And I'm very, very happy
enjoying every minute of it.
I mean, you know what
I've been through, right?
I basically hit rock bottom,
but here I am now,
flying through the clouds.
And maybe you'd like to guess
how I did that.
How, Emilia?
Hmm…
I caught the traitor in our family.
It's Ivy Aguas.
-Ivy Aguas?
-Mm-hm.
What did you do when you found out?
Secret. [chuckles]
Wait. Hold on, Jaguar.
We need to celebrate.
Aren't you even going to, like,
invite me for a drink or something?
We should be happy, right?
-I'll get you some wine.
-Thank you.
[ominous music playing]
[phone alarm ringing]
Hmm?
Whoops.
It's time to make that
very important call.
Okay.
[solemn music playing]
[phone ringing]
[phone continues ringing]
Hello?
Hello, my evil "frenemy."
How are you?
[suspenseful music playing]
Hey, how are the worms there?
Are they disgusting?
I bet it must be so fun
being around them, right?
[laughs]
Hey, come on.
Why aren't you answering me?
So rude. Hello?
Ivy? Say something.
You're always so mad at me.
Now you don't want to answer me.
Mark my words, Emilia.
If I die…
I will haunt you.
That is so scary. Don't do that, okay?
Why are you so mad at me?
When, in fact, I'm doing you a favor.
I'm entertaining you. Because, you know…
you must be so bored there in that coffin.
Boring, right? [chuckles]
But the truth of the matter is…
um, time has passed.
And based on my calculations,
you've only got, like,
three and a half hours left
before you run out of oxygen.
[Emilia] Aw…
Poor you.
Can you survive that?
Well, anyway, I wish you all the best,
and good luck.
And by the way, timer starts now.
Tick-tock. Tick-tock.
[laughs maniacally]
Bye.
[ominous music playing]
[panting]
[tense music playing]
Oh, okay.
[tense music continues]
Jaguar.
Um, I'm really sorry.
But, you know, I have to
reset our date tonight.
Because I just got a phone call from Papa,
and he's asking me to do something.
So, let's reschedule
our drinking session, okay?
And I shall see you soon.
Bye, Jaguar. I'll see you soon.
[ominous music playing]
[phone rings]
-Hello, Dad.
-[Raul] Diego, son.
Ivy Aguas is in danger.
The Ardientes buried her alive.
What? Dad, where is she?
I don't know, son. I didn't ask Emilia.
I don't want her to get suspicious.
What's more important is
you have to find and save her.
You need to find her.
She only has a few hours left.
[tense music playing]
Diego, what did they do to Ivy?
Tell us! What happened to her?
[tense music continues]
[dramatic music playing]
[dramatic continues]
[Ivy] As long as you're all there for me,
I won't lose hope.
I draw strength from you all.
You are the reason why
I will fight to survive.
Why I believe in miracles.
[no audible dialogue]
-Good evening, everyone.
-Good evening, Governor.
-Good evening.
-Hello, Chairman.
Good evening, everyone.
Good evening. I'm glad
you could all make it here.
This is for the centennial celebration
of Poblacion Ardiente.
Inform everyone in your districts.
Tell them we've prepared
a lot of surprises
and tons of prizes.
We're doing this for all the
people of Poblacion Ardiente,
whom I regard as my children.
Friends, I hope to see you there.
Papa had this planned out.
It's going to be a big celebration.
Ardientes!
Oh, Diego, Diego.
How are you, my illegitimate grandson?
Good thing you came.
Uh, Colonel.
You're invited to the
anniversary of the foundation
of our beloved Poblacion Ardiente.
I'm not interested in your shenanigans.
Where is Ivy Aguas?
Bring her out!
[tense music playing]
Diego, why do you care
about Miss Ivy Aguas?
Diego, please.
Why are you asking us for Ivy?
Are you accusing us of hiding her?
How in the world can we do that
when in fact, we're allies?
Honestly, Diego.
You know what, lad?
To prove that we have
no bad intentions or whatever,
we'll help you find Miss Ivy Aguas.
Colonel, tell your men to get ready.
We'll mount an extensive search operation
to find Miss Ivy Aguas.
You liar!
[Emilia] Oh, my…
Hey.
If you did something terrible
to Ivy Aguas,
I'll give you war.
I swear to you, there's going to be war!
He thinks we're capable
of doing something that bad.
I--
Diego, calm down.
Where did you bury Ivy Aguas?
[tense music playing]
[sighs]
[sobbing]
They're all monsters! All of them!
-All of them! Demons!
-[glass breaking]
[sobs]
They buried her alive
just like they did to me before!
Now, my daughter too! Bastards!
You demons!
[somber music playing]
[sobbing]
Damian, I can't take this anymore!
This situation is just too much for me!
I can't act. I can't do anything.
I can't help my daughter because I have to
protect her identity from the Ardientes!
I understand what you're
going through, Camia.
It's like you're trapped
because of all the secrets
you have to keep.
I want to be free
from this secret, Damian.
[somber music continues]
Camia…
Don't you ever put your life in danger.
Now that I'm here, I'll help you.
I'll search for your daughter.
[sobs]
Papa, I'm telling you!
Diego and Ivy Aguas are accomplices!
They just won't admit it straight up!
Ivy and Diego?
They're nothing.
Because I am the governor.
Elected and proclaimed.
So, I don't care if they don't
attend the celebration.
While we celebrate,
the rest of them can all die.
I don't care.
You know, Papa, this is all your fault.
If you just listened to me
over your pet, Ivy Aguas,
then we wouldn't be having this problem.
What is it going to take
for you to stop harping about this?
Okay. I want a position.
I want to be your vice governor.
[tense music playing]
Before that, make sure that Ivy Aguas
can't dig out of her grave.
And bury our enemies' hope
that they still have a savior.
I want you to assure me
that everyone's wonder woman is dead!
[tense music continues]
Jepoy is here.
[Loring] Jepoy.
Diego.
What were you thinking, leaving Ivy alone?
Now, tell me where I'm supposed to look
-because of your failure!
-Jepoy…
-Jepoy, that's enough! Enough.
-Tell me!
I need your help.
I need everyone's help.
Everyone, please spread the news
that Ivy Aguas is missing.
We'll scour the entire province,
and we won't stop until we find her.
-Go now.
-Yes.
We'll coordinate and spread out.
Calm yourself, Diego. Calm down.
Be careful, Nanny.
-[tense music playing]
-[indistinct chatter]
[phone ringing]
[in deep voice] Hello?
Hello. [laughs]
Hi, snake! It's still Emilia.
Why? Did you call anyone?
Mm… Well, I hope not. But even if you did,
there's nothing they can do anyway, right?
Aren't you glad
I left that phone inside that casket?
And you have me for company.
[ominous music playing]
Did you miss me?
You don't know where she is, Diego?
[Anna] Jepoy!
We'll search for her, Jepoy.
The only thing we can do
right now is work together.
We need to cooperate.
[phone rings]
Hello?
Diego, it's me, Ivy.
Ivy.
Help me, Diego.
The Ardientes buried me alive.
I'm coming, Ivy.
Just tell me where you are.
Where are you?
[Emilia] You know, Papa,
no matter how hard
Diego looks for Ivy Aguas,
he'll fail because, you know, she's dead.
Prove it.
-Prove it.
-Okay. Hold on.
[unsettling music playing]
[line busy]
-[line busy]
-What's wrong?
[line busy]
-Maybe there's no reception.
-What?
Yeah. Could be that.
Or she must be dead, Papa.
I don't know. This is so weird.
I don't give a crap
about your many excuses.
What I want from you is the assurance
that Ivy Aguas is in that
plywood box, dead or alive.
[tense music playing]
[groans]
Diego…
Diego, listen.
Listen carefully.
So you can find me.
I'm listening, Ivy.
[Diego] Ivy…
[exhales]
Diego…
Ivy, where are you?
Do you remember…
the place where they kept Jepoy?
[Ivy breathes raggedly]
From there…
Take a right.
Emilia's car took a right.
Then, head straight.
We went straight for a while.
Then…
We hit…
a rough road.
[thuds]
After that, we took a left.
Until…
I heard church bells and tricycles.
[breathing raggedly]
There, Diego.
We entered somewhere.
That's where they buried me.
There. There, Diego.
I'll save you, Ivy.
Promise me you'll hold on.
Promise me you won't give up.
I'll hold on.
I'll… I'll hold on, Diego.
[somber music playing]
I'll hold on…
and I'll wait for you.
[breathes raggedly]
I'll wait for you, Diego.
-I know where Ivy is.
-Where is she?
I'm sure there'll be
plenty of guards there.
To pull this off, I'm going
to need your help, Jepoy.
I'll get some help.
You better make sure this works.
[tense music playing]
Come on. Pick up the damn phone.
[line busy]
[sighs]
[screams angrily]
[door opens]
Emilia, what's wrong this time?
Why are you furious? Just relax.
Don't you tell me to relax.
I'm so stressed right now.
Emilia, I'm here. I'll listen.
What's the problem?
Wow!
When did you ever listen to me?
-[scoffs]
-Do you remember, Raul?
You didn't even visit me in prison.
Emilia, I don't have to
tell you what I did.
But the day you were imprisoned,
I did what I could.
Wow! Really? How sweet.
I don't care anymore, Raul.
I'm very busy preparing for
the celebration of our centennial,
and I'm very busy making sure that
Ivy Aguas will die tonight.
Yes, you heard it right.
She is going to die tonight,
and you're going to help me.
But you know what, Raul?
Don't do anything.
I just realized that Ivy's accomplice,
Diego Torillo, is your son.
So actually, don't do anything.
[scoffs] Seriously, Emilia?
You still don't trust me
and my loyalty to you?
[tense music playing]
Emilia, I know you're very tired.
You're too stressed.
Come here. Stay here.
What's the problem? Huh?
Rest for a bit.
Let's put that here.
Do you want to go on a vacation?
Huh?
[sighs]
Emilia…
Hey.
[unsettling music playing]
[solemn music playing]
[Ivy] I have to get out of here.
For the people.
For justice.
For my mother.
[solemn music continues]
[exhales]
Ivy…
Ivy, hang on.
Hang on, Ivy.
[line rings]
[Anna] He's not picking up, Miss Loring.
I'll try calling Jepoy.
[line rings]
[Anna] He's not picking up, either.
-[line continues ringing]
-[Loring] Where are they?
Where could they be?
[Anna] Their phones just keep ringing.
Miss Camia, Diego and Jepoy
aren't picking up yet.
We have to go, with or without them.
Hold on.
We don't even know where Ivy is.
Where are we going
to start looking for her?
Miss Loring,
what matters is that we do something.
Every second we waste brings
Ivy closer to death's door.
[tense music playing]
Cheers!
Bottles everywhere!
What is this place, a rest house?!
Boss Jaguar, you're alive!
Do I look dead to you?
[laughs mockingly]
-Can a ghost do that?
-Why me, Boss?
Remember, cats have nine lives.
I won't die that easily.
-Long live Boss Jaguar!
-To the boss!
[laughs]
Stop that!
Get your guns.
We're going on a field trip.
-Let's go.
-Move it!
[ominous music playing]
[grunts]
-Did any of you wear this?!
-Mallari did!
Mallari, you're dead meat!
[ominous music continues]
[laughs mockingly]
[tense music playing]
[handbrake clicks]
-[line rings]
-Jepoy, where are you?
We're about to leave.
[Jepoy] Anna, listen to me.
Diego knows where they buried Ivy.
He's with Arthur right now.
And you? Where are you going?
I've got another plan.
I'm looking for help.
We're going to help. We're going to Lily.
-You can't.
-What do you mean, we can't?
I can't just sit here
while my friends need help.
Anna, listen to me.
I know and understand that
we're all worried for Ivy.
But it's suicide to…
barge into enemy territory
without any weapons or backup.
You're safer at the headquarters.
Just stay there. Don't leave.
But, Jepoy…
Just do as I say, Anna.
If Ivy were here, she'd tell you that too.
I hope you get where I'm coming from.
[tense music continues]
[exhales]
[knocking on gate]
Anna…
Diego's on his way to Lily, Auntie Camia.
Jepoy's going to help too.
So, please don't worry.
Lily's going to be safe.
I understand that, Anna.
I know Diego won't let anything happen
to my daughter.
They won't.
I believe that they'll find
and rescue my Lily.
[somber music playing]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Ivy] Do you remember
the place where they kept Jepoy?
From there, take a right.
Turn right.
[Ivy] Head straight.
[Ivy] We went straight for a while.
Just keep going straight.
Ivy, hold on.
Don't give up, Ivy.
[honks]
[Ivy] Then, we hit a rough road.
Diego, are we still on the right path?
We're going to pass through a rough road.
That's what Ivy told me.
[suspenseful music playing]
This is it.
[Ivy] After that, we took a left.
Turn left after the rough road.
[suspenseful music continues]
[Ivy] Until I heard
church bells and tricycles.
[church bell tolls]
Get ready. We're almost there.
You need to relax.
[unsettling music playing]
I'll get you a cup of tea, okay?
It'll help you relax.
Thank you.
[door closes]
[line rings]
Hello, Domingo.
Make sure no one comes near
Ivy Aguas' grave, okay?
I don't care if you have to
guard it for an hour
or a year.
Shoot anyone who approaches her grave.
Understood?
Good.
[ominous music playing]
[ominous music swelling]
[handbrake clicks]
We're here.
Let's go.
[unsettling music playing]
Ivy's here somewhere.
If we have to dig up every grave,
so be it.
As long as we find her.
We have to find her, understood?
Arthur, search that area.
Batch, go that way.
Okay.
Wait, Diego! Wait!
[goon 1] The Ardientes are slave drivers.
They want us to guard
a cemetery at this hour?
What are we supposed to shoot? Zombies?
[goon 2] Stop complaining.
You're getting paid anyway.
We need to move.
We can't just charge them.
We don't have time.
Ivy's going to run out of air!
Do you understand?
-Let's go.
-Wait!
What if they gun us down?!
[tense music playing]
All right, you stay here.
[goon 2] Stay put.
[goon 3] Guard this area.
[tense music continues]
[breathes heavily]
Please answer.
[phone rings]
Ivy… Ivy, we're here.
Don't worry. We'll save you.
Just hold on.
[tense music playing]
Lily's been through so much.
This won't take her down.
You're going to die.
Oh, poor, Ivy.
I'm Ivy Aguas.
I can handle everything.
[Emilia chuckles]
-Hello, Dad.
-Where are you? I'll help you.
We're going to save Ivy
no matter what happens.
[Damian] I'm here to help Ivy Aguas.
[rapid gunfire]
[Camia] She still has to bring
those criminals to justice.